Thank you for watching!
Good evening, everyone.
My name is Ruri Aoi, and I will be conducting today's session. Please give me your best regards.
Hey, Ruri!
Ruri!
This is the 183rd installment of Ukka's 4 Diskfinancier Rem. I would like to deliver another installment with a subtitle.
The subtitle is an original rule of Ukka, in which the subtitle is decided with the users here, and the distribution is based on the subtitle.
The world view is also almost nonexistent.
So that's what we're going to do.
I was told that I could use a strange subtitle this time,
Since I am the facilitator, I thought something about gummy bears would be good.
Gummies!
A strange title for a gummy bear?
It's not weird.
A nice gummy title?
If everyone could think of a nice gummy title, I'd like to give them individuality.
Gummies have personality.
It's good, isn't it?
What do you have in mind? Gentlemen.
A subtitle about gummy bears.
It's hard to come up with one. It's like a comedy.
It's going to be a comedy.
Do you have a unique one?
Wonder Gummy Love.
Gummy gummy gummy gummy.
I don't know how many gummies there are. Oh, that one.
There's three cars and a look back.
Let's gummynicate together today.
Don't you have any idea how to do this?
Gummy communication.
Gummies everywhere.
Blue gummy bears and their merry companions.
That's good, too.
That's for sure.
What do you want?
I don't know.
A festival where vodkas and gummies are both cute.
That's a good idea.
Okay, let's go with that.
Now that the subtitle has been decided, I would like to call the title together.
Se-no, Ukka no,
A fun and fluffy showroom. Ukka and Gummi's Cute Festival.
Yay!
Good evening everyone. This is Ukka.
I, Ruri Aoi, will be in charge of today's proceedings.
I look forward to working with you.
Please give my best regards.
Yes, I'm Yukina. Please give my regards to you.
Yes, I am Rina Murahoshi. Pleased to meet you.
Thank you for watching the 183rd edition of UCCA's delightful and spooky showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Now I would like to tell you about the well-known Maxan time here.
In order for as many people as possible to see this distribution, I will feature it on Twitter from now on, so please repeat it.
Yes, I'll do that.
Okay, so, the pause and the watchword.
The password is a sticker filled entirely with gummy bears.
Amazing.
I'm scared for the people who are about to see it.
Suddenly everyone is saying gummy.
You're being polite.
What should we do about posing?
Like how deliciously we can eat gummy bears.
Like, deliciously.
I mean, do they look delicious?
You can't lose this.
That's right.
You want the gummy title, right?
I won't give up that much.
All right, I'll buy them.
Is that what this is about? Gummi gummi gummi.
That's what I'm talking about.
Well, let's pose for a moment and say, "Demmie's here.
Three, two, one.
What do you think?
Did you get the preconfidence?
I think we got it.
Mizuki just ate two of them.
That's greedy.
Two unions.
I knew about the gminication.
On the way.
I knew about gminication.
Without thinking of the other's gminication.
Not one.
I was,
commercial awareness,
I said, "Why don't you recruit people who see this?
Warm commercial awareness.
It's cute.
It's nice.
I hope you will all join us,
Please retweet the Twitter announcement.
Please do.
I'll let you know what's happening with the group.
I would like to announce the events of the group.
Shall we go to the ranking?
Let's go to the ranking.
Okay, I will announce the ranking.Okay, here are the rankings.
Fifth place, Shumai.
Thank you very much.
In fourth place, Mr. Hohawa.
In third place, Shimao-san from ganyuu!
Thank you very much.
2nd place, Kippa-san.
First place, Shirayu-san.
Thank you very much.
Well, let's put the mark of diffusion once.
Who is it?
Everyone.
Nothing.
Well, I'd like to take a look back at the events of the group,
First of all, today is Wednesday, June 21.
Wrong. Today.
Are you okay?
Today is just after 24:00...Wednesday, June 21, Major Funk Thing.
I'm releasing Unwritten Tweet of Love,
The song is now available.
Have you guys listened to it?
I'm sure you've already heard it.
Yes, they have.
As expected.
It's been 19 hours.
That's right.
You can hear how many hours it is, right?
How many times can I listen to it? During the transmission.
That's it.
Would you like to listen to it now?
It's playing Wonder Little Love.
Let's go!
Zzzz.
Oh, hey...
like this
It's like this, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
I liked it. I like it. I like it.
I like the code too.
Mizu's.
Jambar.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I like it a lot.
Jambar.
He wants to sprinkle.
Next, Ruri's
Oh, this one.
I like it. I like it.
I like it.
Choreography.
Isn't that it?
Okay.
No? Not this way?
Yes, it is.
This way.
This way? Don't be so quick.
Yes, the first one.
You're in trouble, aren't you?
Three back.
One, two, three.
Come on.
Yes, sir.
When are we doing this?
We'll go one by one here.
Let's go!
I can do this.
I like this mistrower.
It's this squishy thing. Like this.
Scan like this.
This is also a heart.
You see a lot of hearts, don't you?
Yes.
Yuka nee, she said, "Let's do that.
Luli will be next.
I'll be there when you show me, Luli.
Come on!
Ready!
It's pretty hard here, isn't it?
It's really hard.
This part is really hard.
This song is available for pre-sale, so please check it out.
The music video for this song will be released at 9:00 p.m. today.
Oh! Oh my god!!!
I'm looking forward to it.
Hey!!!
Is it cute or cool?
What's it look like? But, no, thanks,
You want to go this way next time? Okay, then.
Okay.
Let's see, this time,
The jacket photo of the first single, Manna Little Love, has been released.
This is it,
Ta-da!
Oh!
Clouds!
Nice clouds!Nice clouds!
Clouds.
They say you walk around with a cloud over your head.
It's like this, right?
That's why I wondered how the music video was.
Not at all.
Will the clouds appear or not?
I wonder if clouds will appear or not, and how it will look like,
I think it's something you're interested in, isn't it? Everyone is wondering about that.
Yes, that's right.
Oh! Oh, no!
I don't remember this at all, but I did this star pose.
Do you remember?
I remember. I remember.
Remember?
Yeah, something,
I don't remember it at all.
The one with the feet and hands.
You said it was a walking picture.
Oh, yeah!
Like this.
Yes! Feet and lower part! And then...
Yes, yes!
The balance was difficult.
It was difficult, and I remember it so well, but I wondered if I had done this lineage before.
Yes, the clouds are covered by the eyes,
It is quite a mysterious work.
It's cute, isn't it? But that one.
It's really cute, isn't it?
The clouds are covering his face,
It's cute. It's cute in a unique way.
Hey!
What do you call that music video? What are you allowed to do when you turn the music video around?
Isn't that the first one? The thumbnail?
Thumbnail? There was also a "thumbnail", wasn't there?
Wasn't it a thumbnail?
That was that one.
That's JCET for distribution.
Because that's Momoa-chan. I like everyone so much.
Can I make an announcement? I heard that Momoa-chan and I got lost at the end.
Really?
I was not selected.
Oh, why?
I didn't say that much,
I didn't say that much.
JCET didn't make it to the finals.
That's right.
The preliminaries.
Qualifying was down.
Failed.
That's right.
She became Moa-chan.
But she's so cute.
But the way Moa-chan sings is also impressive.
Is that so?
That's why I thought so.
I thought so too.
Conversely?
But you know what? Ruri's last wanderinra is also impressive,
So that's what it is.
It's becoming a bit of a face.
It's cute.
Please connect.
She's pretty fluttery there, too,
It's whispery, and it's nice there, too.
It's quite difficult.
It's difficult.
Timing and volume.
Yes, indeed.
It's difficult.
I'd like to polish it more from now on.
But you were pretty energetic during Ruri, weren't you?
I was fine.
That's for sure.
After that,
I didn't have it.
So you went away.
I was so excited.
I could do it.
I have to hold back.
Do you have a favorite part?
Like, "I like this part," or "Listen to this girl.
I did, many times,
It was different.
No, it wasn't.
Oh, I'm running away.
I've said it too many times,
The last part of the first verse,
The tips of my eyelashes,
I'm repeating the holidays.
I like that part. I like that part.
That part, too,
Isn't it expensive? The sound.
Isn't it high?
Isn't it high? Sound.
So, yes, I like the height,
And the lyric "I'm repeating you laughing," I really like it,
I like it a lot, so I recommend it.
What about you, Leah?
I like the lyrics,I have a favorite part in the lyrics,
Look at the key meet.
Oh, black.
Together.
Only fingers now.
Key meat.
I love it there.
It's good, isn't it? The lyrics.
Yes, it is. I put it there on the street of my mind.
Isn't "Kitter Clover" a great lyric?
Great lyrics.
What? Like that.
Hey. What is it? Like...
Maybe it's a black bridge. Because, you know,
It's Yotsuba. I don't know.
If it was Yotsuba, wouldn't it be hard to find it?
And we were able to find it together,
That coincidence.
I thought the sense of coincidence was nice.
I thought it was a beautiful lyric.
It's beautiful.
And I can sing.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, you're singing. I'm happy.
You guys made the clover, right?
Yeah.
Like Clover.
Like we're playing Clover.
I thought that was really cool.
It's nice.
Here we are.
It was here.
It was here, wasn't it?
What about you, Chicken?
I don't have a part, but I'm in the choreography for the portrait where I'm singing,
I like the choreography of the part where I'm taking a selfie and everyone is in the picture,
I like that choreography a lot,
I like that choreography a lot.
It's cute,
Do you know if it's like a revival outbreak or something?
What is it?
Why? Was it taken at the time of the PIN occurrence?
It was taken at the time of the code, as a kind of off-shot,
Luli took a selfie before, what was it?
Luli, the selfie-taker, took a selfie with all five members like this,
There are a lot of selfies like this,
I don't know, maybe before Underala came out,
But at that time, there was no choreography, right?
There was no choreography.
When they were doing the choreography.
That's what Ruri said at that time,
Aaah!
You're going to choreograph it! I thought, "I'm going to do the choreography,
I just took the liberty of collecting it on my own.
You're putting it up on the wall on your own?
No one put it up.
I was collecting them on my own.
That's right. That's how I feel about Wonder Little Love.
Please check it out if you like.
Please do.
Yes, please. And now back to the time,
The end.
Lilyway was held at Machida Terminal Plaza Civic Plaza.
Yay!
Here, Wonder Little Love made a presentation,
I'd like to thank all the people who came to the event,
Hey, I'm so happy to see you all!
Machida!
I was so nervous. But I was so nervous that Wonder Little Love was going to perform.
I think it's amazing how nervous you are when you sing a new song for the first time.
But there were a lot of people there who heard the song for the first time,
Well, almost all of them,
I was very happy,
It was a rainy day, but thank you very much.
It was a rainy day, but thank you very much for coming. Thank you for coming.
Oh, yes, it was raining. It was raining.
Bad weather, huh? I got to sleep, didn't I?
I could sleep. It was still inside. It was nice, though.
Was that the first time you used clouds?
Yes, it was!
The cloud party.
Yes, the cloud benefit. We all did the clouds together.
That was amazing!
We did that, and that was fun, too.
That was fun.
That's how Matsuda was.
And one week later, on May 20,
I had another release as Lala Garden and Kasukabe-san.
Oh! Thank you very much.
It was my first time to go to Kasukabe.
Support team.
Saitama Prefecture.
That's right.
I have never been to Saitama Prefecture, and it was the first time for me to go to Kasukabe,
I went there for the first time, but I knew it was the place of "Krion Shinchan," so there was a "Krion Shinchan" at the Kasukabe station from the beginning.
There was a Kurion Shin-chan at the Kasukabe station.
He was cute.
There were Krion Shin-chan everywhere, even at Lala Garden and Kasukabe-san's place,
I thought they were very cute and felt peaceful.I thought it was incredibly cute and it made me feel calm.
Calm.
Wasn't he in the book? I heard you have a kryon shinchan.
I wanted to be there. So, even at the award ceremony.
Today, I felt like I'm still a graceless person.
It's nice, isn't it? I'm glad.
We also had a mimicry contest.
I think Shin-chan is here today.
Shin-chan is here today.
What?
Where is he?
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes. Shin-chan is coming.
Hey, hey, look.
That's Shin-dosuke.
You were just here, weren't you?
Didn't you hear it? Your voice.
I heard it.
You heard it, right?
What?
He was here briefly.
Was he?
Yes.
I didn't see him.
Timing.
Why didn't you just close your eyes?
Just in time.
Another person, another Shin-chan.
Surely there's a Shin-chan pick-up turn.
Should I close my eyes again? What's this?
Are we going to go now?
Hey, hey, look, it's daylight!
What's that? Shin-chan came again? By any chance...
What?
Aren't you doing it fast? He's running away too fast.
You're running away fast. That's funny.
I heard there was at least one more coming.
That's what the rumors said.
I guess we're gonna have to blind them.
I wonder if I'll have to blind them.
Uu, uu, uu, urarashinu suki desu. Nanako onee-san.
Huh?
I heard "Nanako onee-san. And the next one.
I was calling for you.
Is Nanako onee-san there?
I think she went to Nanako onee-san's place.
Oh, so that's how it is. You didn't look for her.
That's nice of you. I'm glad you came.
You should have stayed.
Koba is Hiroshi, father of Shinusuki Nohara. I beg your pardon.
Oh, Hiroshi is here.
Where is your son?
Please go get him.
He was here, at the show game.
But he ran away so fast, it was hard to see him.
Just when you think he's here, he's gone.
Yes, yes, yes.
They were really fast.
Very fast.
Someone is coming.
Someone is coming?
Yasuko-san is here.
Ah, yeah, yeah, you're following me.
This is Yasuko. Yes, I'm Yasuko.
You were here, weren't you?
Yasuko-san was here, right?
And Himawari-chan, Shin-chan's sister, is here.
Himawari-chan?
Himawari-chan's here.
I don't want to see Himawari-chan.
Oh, I saw her. I definitely don't want to see her.
Sorry.
Eh, ~~~~~~~
Eh?
Take your time.
No, no, no.
Not Hinata-chan.
Maybe, Cosmos-chan.
Cosmos?
I don't think she's a sunbather.
Sunflower?
I don't think it was Hinata-chan.
I think there'll be a lot of them.
Goat.
They cry like this, don't they?
But not sunflowers,
Atta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
That's it.
Atta atta atta atta atta atta atta atta.
Atta atta atta atta atta atta atta.
What's this?
Where is the province of the North Star, ata-ta-ta-ta-ta?
Ata-ta-ta-ta-ta.
I don't know.
Generation.
Ata-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
I guess it's like that.
I'm just saying that a lot of them came.I'm just saying we've had a lot of visitors.
Thank you for coming today.
It's amazing.
All at once.
On May 21, right?
Cute Shine.
It's Shine.
It's a cute shine. It's called the Uka-ka-ka version,
Thank you very much.
I was able to do a one-man live performance at the Sangyo Buro Land.
With Kocyunyong-chan,
Can't you see me?
With Kokyunyon-chan,
I was invited to the show with my collaborator, Kokyunyon-chan, and the other three of us,
It was an unexpected collaboration,
How was it? There was a tightening.
He was cute. I kept looking at him.
I was looking at Kogimun.
He was so cute.
A few days before the show,
I went to Sanryo Bureausland again to take pictures of random cheques with goods,
We went to the bureau land again,
I met her there for the first time,
The moment I saw Kogimun-chan,
What?
He was in tears.
That's right. It's a double and triple identity.
Last year,
Pom Pom Pudding and My Melody joined us,
At that time, during the cheque session,
I met Pom Pom Pudding for the first time,
I was so cute that I cried.
So, I hope that next year, or this year,
I thought it would feel good,
I thought it would feel good.
It was too cute,
I thought, "There's such a cuteness in this kind of music,
I was so moved.
She was so cute.
I found Kogimun-chan very cute,
We collaborated. We collaborated during a live performance.
We collaborated with Killer Lips,
I collaborated with Killer Lips and Lucky Happy Everyday,
The part of Killer Lips' song "Tokagekake no Younger,
I collaborated with Killer Lips on the part of "Tokagekake no Younger",
Kogimun was so cute.
We were doing it together, weren't we? They were doing it together.
Poor little guy.
I smiled,
I smiled.
Spilled, spilled, spilled.
Spill, spill, spill.
I know this. Smile.
And Pochacco, too,
He was so friendly.
Yes. And Pochacco, too, he was doing this.
He was so cute.
Healing,
Thank you very much.
He is too cute.
Next year..,
Tuxedo Sam.
I'll see if I can find one.
Pochacco and Cogimun were dancing,
They were so cute.
I heard that they were going to do a unit song with 3 and 3 this time,
They were wearing T-shirts with original arrangements,
There was a lot going on, but what was memorable?
I don't know.
I performed with Reju-chan and Momo-chan,
I played with Reju-chan and Momochan, and there were some parts that I don't usually sing,
I was nervous.
I was nervous, wasn't I? Yes, quite a bit.
We were thinking about it by ourselves,
I think there were probably some unexpected parts.
I think there were some unexpected parts.
I think it was the third chorus.
What was it?
Ondoday.
It was there, wasn't it?
It was really good.
It was good, wasn't it?
It was good. Very good.
There was no 23 there.
Ochitabi no sa,
Cunaiva.
That was the deal.
Coonawaiiwa.
That place was so good.
I couldn't help it.
There are a lot of people who can't listen to the show.
Hurry up.
I guess so.
But Rina, Ayumi and
Sora's fanfare was great.
I was so nervous about the fanfare.
The fanfare was the highlight of the show.
Really?Really?
He was so cool.
He didn't seem handsome at all.
He sang "Otsure" (take me home), didn't he?
Otsure, the next story
The fanfare that rings out for me.
This was cool. I thought.
I didn't think.
It was great.
I was so nervous.
That's how I felt.
Okay, then, let's move on to the planning.
I'd like to move on to the planning.
What's the subtitle?
Vodka and gummy bears are cute!
I think it's cute.
Cute Gummi Festival.
Gummies.
Let's develop new gummies on the theme of cute.
Participants are Rina, Riju, and Yuuzawa.
Please bring various ideas to me, the chairman of the judging committee.
Good ideas.
I will praise a good idea if you give me a good idea. That's the memory of the "new idea".
A new idea.
I would like you to propose some nice gummies that I would like to eat.
I'm looking forward to it.
Gummies, huh?
I haven't developed any. Not yet.
Not yet.
No?
No.
Well, then.
Well, here we go.
Here we go.
Here it comes.
Mackerel in miso sauce.
How is it?
Oh, sure.
What is it? Which way?
Oh, this one, like this.
Ah~.
Right.
Yes.
What is it?
I'm not very good at smoking.
Ah~. So that's what you mean.
I wish you knew what I like.
Popping Shower Gummies.
They look delicious.
They look delicious, don't they?
I want them to crackle in my mouth.
Strawberry and apple mixed gummies.
Same.
It's the same. It looks delicious, so it's Maru.
I think we have to develop a lot of products for Ruri to judge.
I think that's how products are made.
So, here is the first one.
The Ruri group.
With me at the center.
There are many Ruri in the package.
There are a lot of Ruri Ruri in the package.
Like a lot of Ruri Ruri Ruri.
Like a lot of Ruri-chan.
How about this? First of all.
What does it taste like?
It's balloon-y,
Peach and strawberry,
And..,
Jam.
Jam?
Strawberry jam.
Okay, I'll go.
The result of the judgment,
This way.
No good.
Why no?
The reason is, Ruri is missing.
There wasn't enough Ruri.
Too small!
What do you mean?
Without Ruri, it's not cute enough,
I think it's not cute enough.
No good.
That's a tough point.
I have one too.
Here it is.
Natto gummi.
What do you think?
Look! Look!
It's sticky. It's right.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's got gooey stuff too.
Natto gooey?
That's why these are gummy.
This natto.
Never is also a gummy.
And Never, too.
It's all gummy.They are all gummy.
But, they're natto gummies?
Yes.
Oh, no.
No kidding?
I knew it. I knew it, Ruri.
That's harsh.
They're professional gummy bears.
Professional gummy bears.
Because they are professional gummy bears.
I'm pretty much a pro gummy, but I'm here for the pro gummy.
Sushi gummy bears.
Oh! Yes, there are.
But don't they taste different?
Oh, I see.
It means "Sushi Master".
Sushi-flavored gummies.
Oh, so that's what you mean.
Maybe.
So that's what it is.
I like sushi.
That's for sure.
You like Ruri, right?
She likes sushi.
Yeah, I like sushi.
Have you ever thought about it?
Have you ever thought about developing your own gummy bears?
Not really.
I specialize in eating them,
That's right.
Whenever there is a new product, I eat it.
I see.
Lip-shaped KIRARIMPSU gummies.
It would be fun to do this while eating them.
Indeed.
Like that.
You can't sing.
If they were mischievous, I would eat the mischievous ones.
You can't sing that.
Yes, I can.
Okay, Rina-san.
Oh, I told you the title of the song,
Fried egg gummy bears with mayonnaise.
Oh!
Don't you want some Asagi? This one.
No, I'm fine.
I want to eat it!
You want to eat it, too.
I can't eat it sometimes.
Oh, I see. I can't eat them, but you gave them to me.
I thought you might like eggs.
I don't.
But I think I can eat them.
She likes eggs.
Oh, that's right. How about eggs, Muneishi-san?
I like mayonnaise.
Mayonnaise?
Or candy-like.
I also like mayonnaise and candy-like.
Aaaaah!
I think I'd like it too if I ate a simple fried egg gummy,
I'm thinking of eating a fried egg gummy instead of a fried egg.
What?
I was thinking of eating them.
Please eat it.
Yes, but..,
I don't like this mayonnaise.
I don't dislike it. Not at all.
Here you go.
Cloud gummy bears. I like Yuka's Asha-like gummies.
Looks delicious.
There are cloud gummy bears.
Gummy inside a rice cake.
I don't feel like eating rice cake.
That's harsh.
Yes. Then, I'll have the second one.
Ruripyo gummi.
Oh, wow.
Luli likes birds a lot.
I've written quite a few,
I got 5 likes.
Yay!
By the way, don't you like birds?
I wrote this because people call me Luripyo.
She made a motif of me.
What flavor?
Soda flavor.
Oh, that sounds delicious.
It's definitely soda.
Yes, I'm sure.
I chose Luli's favorite gummy.
I like the first one.
Tapioca milk tea gummies.
Wow.
First of all, you can't see the tapioca.
And the outside is a milk tea flavored gummy,
And when you eat the inside, there's tapioca inside. Lots of tapioca.I was eating inside and there's tapioca in it. A lot.
I see.
That's right. How's it taste?
Ding!
I want the good tapioca on the front. Don't hide it inside.
What? But I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to seeing what's inside.
I see.
It won't look like tapioca.
Tapioca doesn't appear in the product,
I'd rather have a product that is built on a sense of acceptance.
Tapioca is intellectual.
So, no?
It's like tapioca.
Rice.
Looks are tough, too.
Ha-ha-ha.
Brown sugar gummies? It looks sweet.
No?
You like sweet things, but you don't have any?
I don't like it that much.
Even though you like them?
I like it, but I can't eat a lot of it.
Oh, I see.
Cider Blue gummies. Blue cider. Cider Blue?
I like the cider blue one.
I mean, isn't that kind of nice?
Is that what you're saying?
My eyes.
Portraits.
Let's do a bar carte.
Matcha milk gummies. Looks delicious.
There aren't many matcha gummies, so it looks delicious.
It's true. I've never heard of matcha gummies.
I haven't.
Then, Riru-san.
Oh, it's not Riru-san.
Here is Riru's third gummy bear.
It's the rice ball gummies that Riru always brings with her.
Riru always brings round rice balls.
No round ones?
It is triangular.
Round ones?
It's triangular.
I saw a round one.
There are round ones, too, right?
Yes, there are.
Today?
I was taking a picture of Tik Tok next to him today,
I was standing next to him, and he had it next to his tripod,
I thought it was a round rice ball.
Triangular.
Square.
I brought the triangles that my mom had done for me,
There was a slight discrepancy.
I see.
Mom's onigiri?
You were looking at it as round or triangular?
Sure.
It's really written. I'm sure of it.
She wrote on a postage stamp today, too.
I saw a big circle.
It's a big circle?
It's a big circle.
Yes, there are a lot of circles.
Like this.
It's a circle!
It's a triangle!
It's definitely triangular!
It's a circle!
But it's shaped like this.
I can see that too.
I can see it,
This is a circle.
It is a circle.
This circle, this circle.
Let's vote.
Certainly.
Does this look like a triangle or a circle?
1 is a circle.
I would like you all to vote with 1 being a circle and 2 being a triangle.
That way, we can see 23 of these, you know, developments.
Yes! Development.
Yes! I wonder if it will be decided.
I wonder if it will be decided.
It's important.
One circle, two triangles.
Then, 1.
One circle.
One circle, two triangles.
Start!
Lulie's, you know, the rice balls I always bring,
If you think this writing is round,
It's 1.
If you think it's triangular, you're a 2. If you think it's triangular, you're 2.
It's definitely triangular.
It's a circle.It's a circle, right?
The apex, the point, and the point-and-shoot.
It's here.
There.
There are no two tenpens.
There is a vertex, and there is a vertex like this, and there is a vertex like this.
This is a triangle.
No, no, no.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Deadline for all of us.
And the result?
Circle!
Circle! Round! Circle!
This is hard!
Round! Round! Round! Round!
Go home, go home!
Look, more than half the people are saying it's a circle.
Doesn't this look triangular to you?
Does it look triangular to you?
On the contrary, about 30% of you call it a triangle.
On the contrary.
That's great.
Thank you. You made it look like a triangle.
They said it was a circle.
It's a circle.
It's not a circle.
It's a strange feeling, isn't it?
I was left with a strange feeling.
I would like to go to the next corner.
The next corner is the Gumilanobe Festival.
Gumilanobe?
Gumilanobe Festival!
Yay!
Let's try various improvised dramas with gummy themes.
Titles are in the box.
Gummy dramas?
Let's write a title like a novel, Gummi.
It doesn't sound like a gummy-themed improvised drama.
I see.
I'll go first.
I'm in charge of gummy bears, so I'll be your representative.
May I show it to you? Here.
Yes.
When I was born again, I was a gummy bear.
Isn't this good?
It's a reincarnation story.
It's good.
Then, I reincarnated as a gummy bear.
It's a dream.
Please.
Delicious!
Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yummy!
Lickety-split.
What are you doing?
I'm eating it!
What are you eating?
Myself!
Myself?
What does it taste like?
Anel?
Oh, is that okay?
What flavor is it, Anel?
Oh, thank you!
Is it good?
A little bit good! A little bit good!
Eat some more!
Oh, wait!
Bye-bye, thank you!
Aah!
Eat!
Fearful English.
I was so surprised.
I thought if it was gummy, it would be gummy,
I thought, "If it's gummy, it's gummy," but he said it was delicious,
I thought he was eating them. Myself.
It was Gummi eating herself, wasn't it?
It was the Anpanman way.
That's how I felt.
It was like "Ten Gummi. Ten Gummi.
If it's heavenly, it's gummy.
But, it seems to be possible. It was a gummy bear.
It was a gummy bear.
Tensei. Tensei.
Tensei.
Wasn't it Tensei?
Was it Tensei?
I learned something.
I learned a lot.
Next, Rina.
A restaurant whose menu is nothing but gummy bears.
Michelin ride.
Ride Michelin?
Michelin is like a good restaurant, right?Michelin is like a good restaurant, right?
Is that what it means?
You mean a restaurant gets a Michelin rating?
It's a happy world.
Customer.
Corner.
Well, you know, to be able to come to L'Iserean,
I'm happy.
Happiness.
Well, thank you.
Well then..,
Hello?
Uh..,
What is it?
These pickled cucumber gummies..,
Do you have it?
This is a very special item on our menu,
Actually, it is stuck on a stick.
Oh, my God! I love it!
It was so popular on social networking sites that it spread. It went viral on social networking sites and spread all over the place.
This was in Tokyo, congratulations!
Congratulations!
I loved it even back then. I loved it even back then.
I really appreciate you saying that,
We're pretty hungry for spaghetti,
Spaghetti?
It's not sweet.
I just realized something good.
This way.
These are meat sauce gummies.
Meat sauce gummies?
Not gummies, but spaghetti.
Regular spaghetti?
Ah! Spaghetti!
Spaghetti.
I see.
This is a spaghetti only gummy.
Oh, there is sauce, too.
It's a gummy that you can eat only noodles without sauce.
Ah, fascinating.
Isn't it attractive?
But I would like to have soup, too.
Soup is a good appetizer.
Surely, there are things that go well with soup.
I wonder what kind of soup goes well with it.
What goes well with soup?
These are corn gummies.
Corn gummies?
These are gummy bears with lots of gummy corn inside corn soup.
Gummy corn in corn soup.
Is there nothing but gummy corn here?
I don't like it.
There's nothing but gummy bears here.
No, no, no. Wait a minute.
One more.
Wait a minute.
Can I go through one more?
Yes. Excuse me.
It goes perfectly with that,
Hochicha gummies.
Thank you very much.
No way.
I did it.
There were delicious-looking gummies. Lots of them.
This was the one that caught my attention the most.
When I opened the menu, this was the first thing that came up.
I was thinking of it for the project I was working on earlier,
It just happened.
I couldn't get it out.
Okay, Riz.
I wonder what it is.
What is it?
It's long.
My boyfriend proposed to me with a gummy bear on his ring finger instead of a ring.
Boyfriend
Boyfriend.
Am I your boyfriend?
I play the girlfriend
Well then...
You have it, don't you?
Okay, here we go.
What's the matter? You called me out here.
I've been meaning to tell you something all day.
What?
Reeju, marry me!
What? Wait a minute.
If you look closely...
What...
It's kind of squishy.
You can eat it.
Eatable...
This isn't wedding candy...
Wait a minute!
Oh, my God!
What?
What are you doing? Lisieux!
Who are you?
Who are you?Who are you!
Who are you!
Will you marry me...
Marry me!
So you'll just...
Set me up in my dream?
Yes.
Stop it! I'm the one who's gonna fuck you! I'm a peanut!
I taste like Coke!
You taste like Coke!
Stop it, Peachy!
No, no, no, no, no! Wait!
I got it!
That's a line!
That's the line!
Oh, it's eaten!
Yum!
It's good!
Oh, man!
Oh!
That was a scene!
I don't want to do that at all!
Happiness is in the air!
Ta-da! That's great!
I'm so happy!
Thank you! Does this mean I can have a prefectural group?
Congratulations!
It's the Gummi God.
Thank you, Gummi God.
Yay! I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
Ending.
That's all for this project.
This is the 183rd edition of Ukka's Delightful and Unwindy Showroom.
It's ending in the blink of an eye.
It's early.
Please make an announcement.
Juice-Juice's 1,000,000 1 Live will be at Shibuya Beats on Saturday, September 30 and at Tokyo Kinema Club on Saturday, October 14,
Sunday, July 21 at the Big Hit Room.
I would appreciate it if you could make your schedule.
Please keep your schedules open.
The release of the album is now underway,
On May 28th at Morishita Chidanuma,
On June 4, we will be at the Salt Stop Salt Festival and Underground Walkway.
On June 10, Nara Bozu and Tatsuhide Tsuchikawa.
On June 11, Kobe.
This is a difficult one.
On June 11, it is Kobe Clock.
Yes.
There will be an online signing on May 31,
Please check it out. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Next,
On June 3, Saturday,
at Studio Freedom in Shibuya,
Rinna Yuki's birthday solo live, "What's is?
What's is?
The second part, "Happy Oerolie!
The cute traffic jam is about to begin.
It will start.
It is now on sale.
It's coming soon.
I'm rehearsing.
We've been rehearsing, and I'm starting to realize that what I had been feeling was pretty much like this,
I'm just starting to realize that it's pretty much like this,
Now we're working on putting it all together.
I can see the whole picture now.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sure it will be different,
I think it will be totally different.
Please look forward to it. Please do.
That's it, today at 9:00 p.m,
music video of Wonder Little Love will be available for preview.
Premiere release.
It will premiere.
The music video, everyone, at 9:00 p.m. as it is,
I hope you will be able to see it on Uka's YouTube page.
Thank you very much.
That is all.
I would like to announce the final racking.
Please do so.
Fifth place, kitto.
Thank you very much.
In 4th place, Gaiinyu no shi no otanii-san.
3rd, Shibarie-san.
Thank you very much.
2nd place, Shirai-san.
1st place, Risaku-san.
Thank you very much.
The next broadcast will be on Wednesday, September 7 at 7:00 pm.
To make sure you don't miss it, please mark your heart and register it as a favorite.To make sure you don't miss any delivery, please mark your heart and subscribe to your favorites.
Also, please check out our personal distribution.
Best regards.
No matching.
No reflection card today.
How did you feel?
I was happy. I was in a world full of gummy bears.
I was happy. How was it?
It looks delicious.
But it was a pretty good development.
I think it was pretty good in my opinion.
There is a possibility that we may be developing it ourselves.
In the future.
It will be released. I am sure of it.
I am waiting with anticipation.
Yes, we are. It's like this.
And so, this is the end of the 183rd edition of Uguka's Yukkari Riff-Raff Showroom.
This delivery, this, this delivery, ha, yes.
There will be no reflection card for the rest of the delivery, so I'll leave you all here.
That's all for now, Uka. Bye bye!